<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Ayham Alzoubi]]></title>
  <link href="http://AyhamAlzoubi.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://AyhamAlzoubi.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-12-08T19:34:47+04:00</updated>
  <id>http://AyhamAlzoubi.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Ayham Alzoubi]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[One Year In UAE]]></title>
    <link href="http://AyhamAlzoubi.github.com/blog/2012/12/08/one-year-in-uae/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-08T18:27:00+04:00</updated>
    <id>http://AyhamAlzoubi.github.com/blog/2012/12/08/one-year-in-uae</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I came to UAE in 8-12-2011 to visit some relatives and search for suitable job.</p>

<p>It was very good experience to come to Dubai and stay in the fastest growing country in the world,
and to see life organization in this country.</p>

<p>After this year of life in Dubai there is a question many people ask me about:</p>

<h3>Is UAE the best country to live in?</h3>

<p>The answer to this question not easy, but from my point of view I can put several negative and positive points, i will start with the positive points:</p>

<ul>
<li><p>Dubai is miniature model about business all over the world.</p></li>
<li><p>In Dubai you can see and work with people of all nationalities in the world.</p></li>
<li><p>In Dubai you can live a good life and all your needs and hopes are available.</p></li>
<li><p>In Dubai you can get good work experience (depends on your position and the company you are working in).</p></li>
<li><p>You can have good friends from other your country.</p></li>
</ul>


<p>And other good points&#8230;</p>

<h6>In the other side, i will reserve some of negative points and mention some:</h6>

<ul>
<li><p>In Dubai you live away from home, your family and old friends.</p></li>
<li><p>You cann&#8217;t do any plan for your future in this country because you will leave someday.</p></li>
<li><p>You may suffer from some of the political problems between your country UAE.</p></li>
<li><p>Its very hot in UAE, and the weather is very difficult.</p></li>
</ul>


<p>And other points i cann&#8217;t say for now &#8230;</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook In This Blog]]></title>
    <link href="http://AyhamAlzoubi.github.com/blog/2012/10/30/adding-facebook-application/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-30T22:55:00+04:00</updated>
    <id>http://AyhamAlzoubi.github.com/blog/2012/10/30/adding-facebook-application</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Now you can use this blog to like my facebook page and you can post on my facebook wall.
Adding new facebook application to your blog needs some steps from you to do:
Create facebook application <a href="https://developers.facebook.com/apps" title="Facebook App">fb-App</a> and get application ID.</p>

<p>.</p>

<p>.</p>

<p>.</p>

<p>.</p>

<p>.</p>

<p>.</p>

<p>.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
